utoypia.com 2003-06-04

# uTOYpia - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:** **Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the utoypia.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Email address 
  * Phone number 
  * Credit/Debit Card Information 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We only use your e-mail address to send out promotional offers and sale information that relates directly to our store. We never share your e-mail address with any outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13. 

**How You Can Correct Your Information**

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [service@utoypia.com](mailto:service@utoypia.com)
